Samantha Dickeson

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Current student at Founders and Coders, learning JavaScript web development. I like making things, solving problems and making things that solve problems. I'm a Psychology graduate, and before learning web development I worked in data analysis for four years, teaching myself SQL, VBA and a smattering of Python.

FOUNDERS AND CODERS

Founders and Coders, Finsbury Park

MARCH 2019 - JULY 2019

Founders and Coders are a non-profit based in Finsbury Park, London. They run peer-led full-stack web development courses which are free but highly selective.

There is a heavy focus on cooperation and all our coding is done by pair programming.

I'm looking forward to gaining design and build sprint experience working on some exciting <u>tech for better</u> projects with my fellow students in the coming weeks.

EXPERIENCE

Vanguard Learning Trust, Ickenham — *Data Manager*

DECEMBER 2015 - MARCH 2019

My responsibilities included analysing student performance data for target setting and reporting to senior leadership. I gained a lot of experience in MS Excel and Google Sheets, teaching myself VBA and Google Apps Script to create dynamic reports and data visualisations.

Xerox UK, Uxbridge — Data Migration Analyst

MARCH 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

I managed qualification related data on the company data system SAP. As I picked up VBA and SQL, I began to produce mini 'applications' for employees and managers to access and transfer data.

My github is:

■ github.com/starsuit

See my favourite projects:

■ starsuit.netlify.com

Email me:

■ samlucydickeson@gmail.com

Find me on linkedin:

■ linkedin.com/in/samantha-dickeson

STACK / SKILLS

- HTML and CSS
- Accessibility and design
- Git and GitHub
- Vanilla JavaScript
- Test-driven development
- Pair programming
- Node and npm
- Express
- Handlebars
- PostgreSQL
- Heroku deployment
- React
- A little bit of Python

EDUCATION

Reading University — BSc Psychology 2:1

OCTOBER 2010 - JUNE 2014

Vyners School, Ickenham SEPTEMBER 2003 - JULY 2010



@starsuit



@star_suit



@Starsuit